

# **RAFAEL MORALES**

Digital Marketer International MBA in Digital Marketing

## PERSONAL HISTORY

Professional with a total of 7 years of work experience. More than 3 years of experience in the technology industry and 2 years working in digital marketing, leading eCommerce projects, website development, design and execution of SEO, social media management and inbound marketing strategies.

## SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- SEO & SEM
- · Inbound Marketing
- · Analytics & Monitoring
- · Remarketing

## PLATFORMS AND TOOLS

- Google Analytics + Google Tag Manager
- Google Console + Google Ads
- WordPress + WooCommerce
- Facebook Ads / Store + WApp Business

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **SEO & eCommerce Manager Freelance**

Active Visions Group | Jan 2020 - Present

- Creation, management and execution of SEO strategy.
- Creation of the eCommerce site using WordPress and Woocommerce.
- · Design and execution of inbound marketing strategy.

## **Digital Marketing Manager Freelance**

Iluminar | 11/2018 - Present

- Increased repeat buying from 10% to 35%.
- Achieved a 300% ROI digital marketing conversion campaigns.
- Sales margin improved by 22% after implementation of online sales channels and inbound marketing strategies.

#### **BI Consultant**

### Zeus Tecnología | Jun 2015 - Oct 2018

- Development of the financial panel to end-user increased the license acquisition of BI department by 25%.
- Elaborated more than 60 personalized ad-hoc reports to customers from different industries: hospitality, retail, manufacturing, health, travel, etc.

## **CONTACT INFO**

WhatsApp: <u>+57 3052661440</u> rafaelmorales112@hotmail.com Current Location: Bogotá, Colombia

My Portfolio

## **EDUCATION**

#### M.Sc. International MBA

ESIC Business & Marketing School - SISU | 2018 - 2020

#### M.sc. Tax Managemet

Universidad Tecnológica | 2017 - 2018

#### **B.Sc. Business Administrator**

Universidad del Norte | 2009 - 2014